Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series III: Production Files
  - Subseries C: Mabou Mines-related productions
    Oversize production files from Mabou Mines-related productions.
    - Voyage of the Beagle poster: preservance Theatre, Douglas, AK, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 936)
    - Poster - Philip Glass performance, 11/15/72, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 2381)
  - Subseries D: Mabou Mines film productions
    - Dead End Kids credits galleys, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 2375)
    - Dead End Kids audio recording cue sheets, undated (Box 139, Folder 2376)
- OVERSIZE Series IV: Photographs
  - Subseries A: Production photographs
    Oversize documentary photographs of Mabou Mines productions.
    - Dressed Like an Egg Richard Landry; prints, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1221)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice prints; Japan, undated (Box 31, Folder 1222)
    - The Saint and the Football Players prints, undated (Box 31, Folder 1223)
    - Company photos print, undated (Box 31, Folder 1224)
- OVERSIZE Series VIII: Touring Files
  - Subseries A: Touring Files by Production
    Oversize touring files: mostly light plots, maps, and posters.
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Apr 1981; UC Santa Cruz posters (Box 44, Folder 1619)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice / Hajj Aug 1984; Japan tour maps (Box 44, Folder 1620)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1-4, 1985; Kent State University maps, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 1621)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 17-18, 1985; University of Tennessee, Chattanooga maps (Box 44, Folder 1622)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 3, 1985; Poughkeepsie, NY track sheets (Box 44, Folder 1623)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 7-10, 1985; University of Hartford light plot, maps, brochures (Box 44, Folder 1624)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 11, 1986; University of Vermont, Burlington light plot, track sheets, venue brochures (Box 44, Folder 1625)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 14, 1986; Williams College, Williamstown, MA track sheets (Box 44, Folder 1626)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC light plot, track sheets (Box 44, Folder 1627)
    - Cold Harbor Sep-Oct 1986; University of Iowa, Iowa City track sheets (Box 44, Folder 1628)
    - Cold Harbor [Sep-Oct?] 1986; Soutwest Missouri State University, Springfield, MO light plots, track sheets (Box 44, Folder 1629)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Vallodolid, Spain theater plans (Box 44, Folder 1630)
    - Cold Harbor Aug 1987; Port of History Museum, Philadelphia light plot (Box 44, Folder 1631)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Oct 9, 10, 1987; St. Louis, MO track sheets (Box 44, Folder 1632)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Stockton State College, NJ light plots (Folder 1)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 1985; Owensboro, KY light plot (Folder 15)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 17-18, 1985; University of Tennessee, Chattanooga light plots (Folder 14)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; Catamount, St. Johnsbury, VT light plot (Folder 13)
    - Cold Harbor Nov 1985; University of Massachusetts at Amherst light plot (Folder 12)
    - Cold Harbor Feb-Mar 1986; Theatrical Outfit, Atlanta, GA ground plan/light plot (Box map case, Folder 1642)
    - Cold Harbor Mar 26-30, 1986; Charleston, SC map (Folder 3)
    - Cold Harbor Oct 7, 1986; University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign light plot, track sheets (Folder 2)
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; UC Davis light plot/ground plan, track sheets (Folder 10)
    - Cold Harbor Nov-Dec 1986; Humboldt State University, Arcata, CA light plots, ground plans (Folder 9)
    - Cold Harbor Jan 1987; Theatre Artaud, San Francisco, CA light plot, track sheets (Folder 8)
    - Cold Harbor May 1987; Valladolid, Spain light plot, ground plan, track sheets (Folder 7)
    - Company Sep 22-25, 1987; University of Texas at Austin light plot, track sheets (Folder 6)
  - Subseries D: Organizations and Festivals
    Oversize files relating to national and international theater organizations and festivals.
    - American Center in Paris ground plan, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1633)
    - New York International Festival of the Arts press, poster, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 1634)
    - Sundance Institute poster, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 1635)
    - Yellow Springs Institute poster, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1636)
    - Beckett Festival light plot, undated (Folder 2)
- OVERSIZE Series X: Press
  - Subseries A: General Press
    Oversize press items about the company generally, and about awards and nominations.
    - Vogue Jul 1972 "New Physical Theater" by Barbara Rose (Box 49, Folder 2033)
    - Obie Awards May 26, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 2034)
    - LA Weekly May 11, 1984 (Vol 6 No 24) "Women in Film" issue (Box 139, Folder 2377)
    - "Works" Wexner Center performing arts catalog, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 2378)
  - Subseries B: Company Members & Associates
    Oversize press items about company members.
    - Akalaitis various Oct-Dec 1989 re: "The Seasons" (Box 49, Folder 2035)
    - Breuer Village Voice May 19, 1987 "American Theater's Wild Man" (Box 49, Folder 2036)
    - Breuer Bomb Summer 1996 (Box 49, Folder 2037)
  - Subseries C: Productions
    Oversize press items about Mabou Mines and related productions.
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Interview Jun 1988 (Box 49, Folder 2038)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Artforum Sep 1984 (Box 49, Folder 2039)
    - Lear New York Times Magazine Sep 10, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 2040)
    - Lear Lower Manhattan Cultural Council Downtown Arts Activities Calendar Jan 1990 (Box 49, Folder 2041)
    - Warrior Ant New York Times Magazine Nov 9, 1986; Oct 16, 1988, 1986, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 2042)
- OVERSIZE Series XII: Financial Files, Grants, and Development
  - Mabou Mines Development Foundation general accounting journal, 1973-1979 (Box 140)
  - Quotidian Foundation / Mabou Mines Development Foundation financial journal, 1979-1982 (Box 140)
  - Film Journal, 1982-1983 (Box 140)